http://www.dhsdiecast.com/privacy.asp

We are OPEN for business! New items are arriving on a regular basis and we will continue to fill orders.
Kids Zone
DISCOUNTED ITEMS!
Vintage Merchandise!
Privacy Policy Statement
This is the web site of DHS DIECAST.
Our postal address is
107 Karl St.
Berea, OH 44017
We can be reached via e-mail at info@dhsdiecast.com
or you can reach us by telephone at 800-591-1171
DHS DIECAST COLLECTABLES AND YOUR PRIVACY
Information on this Web site may contain inaccuracies or typographical errors. The information presented may be changed or updated without notice. DHS Diecast may also make improvements and/or changes in the products, descriptions and/or pricing described in this information at any time without notice.
Please note that DHS Diecast does not want to receive confidential information from you through our Web site. Any information or material sent to DHS Diecast will be considered NOT confidential. By sending us any information or material, you grant us an unrestricted, irrevocable license to use, reproduce, display, perform, modify, transmit and distribute those materials or information.
You should know that DHS Diecast will not release your name or other information to others unless: (a) we obtain your permission to use your name or other information; or (b) we are required to do so by law or (c) we use aggregate information for sales and marketing reporting purposes. For example, we may say that x percent of our audience is from outside the United States and y percent is from inside.
Links and Advertising
DHS Diecast makes no representations whatsoever about any other Web site which you may access through this one. When you access a non-DHS Web site, please understand that it is independent from us, and that we have no control over the content on that Web site. In addition, a link to a non-DHS Web site does not mean that we endorse or accept any responsibility for the content, or the use, of such web site. It is up to you to take precautions to ensure that whatever you select for your use is free of such items as viruses, worms and other items of a destructive nature.
IN NO EVENT WILL DHS DIECAST COLLECTABLES, INC. BE LIABLE TO ANY PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR OTHER CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES FOR ANY USE OF THIS WEB SITE, OR ON ANY LINKED WEB SITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY LOST PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF PROGRAMS OR OTHER DATA ON YOUR INFORMATION HANDLING SYSTEM OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF WE ARE EXPRESSLY ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES
Security
We exercise great care in providing a secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. When credit card information is transmitted we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption.
Your DHS Diecast Collectables, Inc. Account is password protected so that only you can access it and view the member information relevant to the account. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone.
DHS Diecast will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or email. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information.
You Accept These Terms
By using this site, you show your acceptance to the DHS Diecast Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the DHS Diecast site following changes to these terms will mean you accept the changes.
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Web site privacy statement, you should contact the company as follows: President, DHS Diecast Collectables, Inc., 107 Karl St., Berea, Ohio 44017; or via email at info@dhsdiecast.com.
Company Information
About Us
Privacy Policy
Site Map
My Account
Login / Register
View Cart
Customer Service
Copyright © 2014, DHS Diecast Collectables, Inc.
